
{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "What is JavaSript ?",
      "answer": [
        "A programming language.",
        "A country.",
        "A .",
        "A programming language."
      ],
      "correct": 0,
      "points": 20,
      "level": 1,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "When JavaScript was created ?",
      "answer": ["1995"],
      "correct": 2,
      "points": 50,
      "level": 2,
      "type": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who invented JavaScript ?",
      "answer": [
        "Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi",
        "Brendan Eich",
        "Steve Jobs",
        "Chef Moha"
      ],
      "correct": 1,
      "points": 50,
      "level": 2,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Java === JavaScript ?",
      "answer": ["True", "False"],
      "correct": 1,
      "points": 20,
      "level": 1,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the first name of JavaScript when it was released ?",
      "answer": ["MOCHA"],
      "correct": 1,
      "points": 100,
      "level": 3,
      "type": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is SQL ?",
      "answer": ["Programming language", "Mocha", "LiveScript"],
      "correct": 0,
      "points": 50,
      "level": 2,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Is angular a frontend framework ?",
      "answer": ["True", "False"],
      "correct": 0,
      "points": 20,
      "level": 1,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "React is based on...",
      "answer": ["HTML", "JavaScript", "Dart"],
      "correct": 1,
      "points": 20,
      "level": 1,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What HTML stands for ?",
      "answer": [
        "Home Tool Markup Language",
        "Hope Test Mate Language",
        "Hyper Text Markup Language"
      ],
      "correct": 2,
      "points": 50,
      "level": 2,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of our class",
      "answer": ["Alan turing", "Brendan Eich", "Ada lovelace", "YouCode 2/2"],
      "correct": 1,
      "points": 20,
      "level": 1,
      "type": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How Old were Elon musk when he became the richest person on earth ? ",
      "answer": ["49", "50", "55", "48"],
      "correct": 0,
      "points": 100,
      "level": 3,
      "type": 0
    }
  ]
}